It seems today
that all you see
Is violence in movies
and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy.
Wow, dinner smells great, Lois.
What'd you make?
Nothing. I just defrosted
one of the casseroles
Bonnie left on our porch
after my foot got infected.
Most of our meals are donated
stews born of trauma.
Well, I had a scary day.
During my science lab,
a whole beaker of chemicals
almost blew up right in my face.
Oh, my God!
Look at this peanut.
It's got three peanuts in it.
Peter, stop bringing
snack foods to dinner.
How was everyone else's day?
My day was awful!
I had to give
an oral book report
in front of my English class,
but it was right when I...
was at full mast.
Okay, next up is Chris Griffin.
My report is on Tom Sawyer.
"A modern-day warrior,
"mean, mean stride,
"today's Tom Sawyer,
mean, mean pride."
That is a song by Rush.
I don't know, man, I googled it,
and that's what came up.
Well, as much as I'd love
to sit and hear more
about my son's public wood show,
me and the guys have a tee time.
A tee time? But it's dark out.
Miniature golf, Lois.
And it's gonna be a blast.
Even more fun than a Blow Pop.
I never should've married it.
Once they say "I do,"
they don't.
Ah, man, nothing better
than hanging out with my pals
on a Tuesday night.
Hey, why... how come we always
do stuff together on Tuesdays?
It's when America unloads
all its week-old tacos.
Sure, Congress can push
through "Taco Tuesday,"
but we can't seem to get
decent Medicare reform.
Those two things are
unrelated, Joe.
Says the shill for Big Taco.
Should've played through
that birthday party.
They're playing way too slow.
Could we please have
some quiet on the greens?
Whoa, Chris, what's going on?
Where are you going?
I can't take the humiliation.
I think my only option is
to move away forever.
What? Wh-- Is this about what
happened with your book report?
The teasing was awful, Brian.
Even Principal Shepherd
got in on it.
Chris Griffin,
please report to woodshop.
Stop it.
I'll stop
when they stop laughing.
My approval rating
is through the roof.
Just like Chris Griffin's rod.
On a more somber note,
that kid with the helmet die.
Chris, you can't just run away
from your problems.
Well, I can't just move on
and pretend nothing happened.
This isn't a school shooting.
Okay, I see you're upset.
And I wouldn't suggest this
if it weren't so serious, but...
Look, Stewie and I
built a time machine.
You did? How?
Well, you know, I was always
really good at Legos,
and I-I think it just kind of
snowballed from there.
You know, if I have any advice,
it's keep building, Chris.
Keep building.
Anyway, maybe you and I travel
back in time to this morning
and give you a do-over
on your book report.
That would be amazing.
Did Rupert come this way?
Son of bitch killed his wife
and he's blaming
an eight-armed man.
Brian's gonna let me use
his time machine
-to re-do my book report.
-Oh, is that right?
And how exactly
is Brian going to do that, hmm?
-With his time machine?
-Hey, I handed you a wrench.
Yeah, the wrong wrench.
Just stay away from it.
Hey, guys, you know
what might be fun?
We should all pool our money
and buy some
scratchers together.
-I love that idea.
-Yeah, it'd be a great way
to cap off
our Tuesday Guys' Night.
Oh, speaking of that, we've got
a special on tacos today.
Let's keep your politics
out of this, pal.
Ah, you guys go ahead.
I'd rather spend my money
on this tightly-curled
horoscope scroll.
Suit yourself.
Here we go, winning combo.
Kim Kardashian...
Khloé Kardashian...
Scott Disick.
I'll try my favorite,
Dignity Dollars.
Martin Luther King...
Malcolm X...
Aww. Jussie Smollett.
Let me show you how it's done.
Give me one of the Bald Bucks.
Piven...
Travolta...
Cage.
-I'm a winner!
-Awesome.
We won $123.
Split three ways,
that's 41 bucks apiece.
That's fine. I'm happy
with my horoscope scroll.
"Be sure to gamble today
with your handicapped,
horny and Black friend."
That-that could mean anything.
"Also, close your search tabs
before your big work
presentation tomorrow."
Bunch of mumbo jumbo.
As you can see,
third-quarter sales-- uh...
Oop, uh, sorry about that.
Yeah, let me just, uh...
Okay, I-I don't know
how that, uh...
Ah, just give me
one second here.
A-As I was saying,
third-quarter...
I apologize
for the slight, uh...
A mini-mart scroll warned
of this. I'll clean out my desk.
I don't know, Brian.
Stewie said to stay away
from the time machine.
Don't worry about Stewie.
Okay, just put in today's date,
set the time and go.
DNA mismatch.
Enter secondary voice password
within 20 seconds
to prevent self-destruct.
Crap. Secondary password?
Self-destruct?
Wait, wait, wait. I got this.
Zac Efron.
Um, Susan Lucci.
Uh, uh, uh, Dora. Diego.
Gold's Gym.
-Mykonos.
-Oh, I-I know, I know.
Fabulous. Fab. Totally fab.
Uh, uh, go, bitch.
Whatever, bitch.
Love you, bitch.
Um, yes, queen.
Yas, queen.
Y-Yas, queen.
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Did you see that?
Check it out, Chris.
Welcome to 16 hours ago.
So, how does it feel
to be living in the past?
Wow. Look how small
that tree is.
And how old all those cars look.
Oh, yeah, there's gonna be a lot
of very small differences
like that.
Hold on, I-I thought we were
gonna time travel to my school,
not to our house.
Oh, yeah, I just plugged in
what was on the tag
on my collar.
That's the only address I know.
Wait a minute,
this could be amazing.
We got a few hours
before your book report.
And with a day's advantage,
we can use that time
to bet on sports,
already knowing the outcome.
Oh, my gosh, you're right.
Okay, hang on, hang on, hang on.
Ah, here we go. WNBA.
There's a Mystics-Sparks game
today.
Remember who won that?
I don't even know
what city they're from.
Which one has Caitlin Clark?
I-I don't know.
Both of them? Neither?
Man, she's the best, maybe.
Hey, Cleveland.
You look different.
Yeah, with my scratcher
winnings,
I was able to buy
$41 of Ozempic.
Donna thinks I'm starting
to look like skinny Jonah Hill.
And just like Jonah Hill,
I can't wait
to be an aggressively unstable
relationship partner.
I see. Must be nice
to have money to burn.
I wouldn't know.
Say, guys, I forget,
how many people does it take
to make a thing go right?
It takes two
to make a thing go right.
I think you knew the answer.
Thanks to those
lucky scratchers,
I just bought Now That's
What I Call Music! volume 12.
Game, cassette, match.
Hey, check it out, guys,
I turned those winning
scratchers into a new belt.
TJ Maxx was having a sale
on everything
-that's strewn on the floor.
-Great.
Seems like everybody's really
enjoying their big winnings.
You can't wear that shirt
because of my therapy.
I got her right under
my pudgy, nonthreatening thumb.
Okay, it's almost time
for your English class.
We just have to head off
your past self
so you can give
the book report instead.
Sounds good. Whoa, I guess
if I have anything to say
to Derek, I should say it now.
I have nothing to say to Derek.
Oh, here I come.
Chris, uh,
you can't go in there.
Brian, what are you doing here?
Are you me?
Look, there's not much time.
We're from the future.
Well, your future, our present.
Let me stop you right there.
I am 100% fine
with whatever this is.
I just go where I'm told.
Okay, Chris, get in there
and make this
the flaccid-est report
of your life.
I won't let you down.
Just in time, Chris. You're up.
Not today I'm not.
Hello, peers. This is my report
on the book Tom Sawyer.
The cover shows a kid
painting a fence.
And inside it is paper,
which is made from trees.
- The end.
- -Chris, I may have to fail you.
Well, that's all good,
'cause the only chub in town
is the insurance company. Kobe!
Quagmire, I see you're wearing
a brown belt today.
Did you buy another one?
Nope, same belt. Reversible.
That just blew my damn mind.
Belts are reversible,
men are becoming women,
I'm kind of getting into it,
what's this world coming to?
Evening, gentlemen.
Thought I'd offer
some celebratory popcorn shrimp
for the big scratcher winners.
Wow, no way!
That's the appetizer
in commercials
most likely to fly
through the air.
Any food that's airborne
on television is very special.
Peter, come on, have some.
I understood the shrimp to be
exclusively for winners.
Damn it! It's not fair.
I got to find a way to have
what they have.
Okay, suction cups.
Pulley system.
Carabiners. Rope. Ski mask.
And one last thing: a bat.
I-I don't understand
the crossword ones.
Well, Chris,
probably time to head home.
And congrats again
on a successful,
non-turgid book report.
Please stop saying
gross smart words.
Uh, hey... is, uh,
is there maybe something
you guys want to tell me?
Yeah. Did you know there was
a WNBA game yesterday
between the Mystics
and the Sparks?
Yes, of course.
The Mystics crushed
the Sparks by 26 points.
Aw...
Yeah, huge upset.
Vegas had it all wrong.
Aw!
Listen, I know
you're probably mad
we took the time machine
without asking,
but, trust me,
there's nothing to worry about.
You sure about that?
Uh, sorry, little guy.
Mom thinks it'll help
the swelling from the burns
if I put some of your
diaper cream on my face.
Looks like Brian
and Chris kicked up
a little more than dust
on their mosey back in time.
Now, please consider
these fine commercial products.
Whip sound effect.
Yeah, he probably wasn't
supposed to read
that last part.
Yeah. There, you see?
There it is.
Holy crap! What happened?
We-we didn't even see Meg
in the past.
Well, Brian...
I would surmise that
in the original timeline,
the laughter at Chris
emanating from his classroom
created a distraction...
So by turning her head
slightly to investigate,
Meg kept her face from being
directly over the explosion.
But in a timeline
where Chris was unaroused...
...the distracting laughter
was absent.
Come on! Not one bag of pot
in any of these things?
So with no noise
coming from Chris's classroo,
Meg never turned her head away,
ensuring that her face
would absorb
the full brunt of the explosion.
It's a weird word. "Brunt."
Such a dumb language.
I feel horrible.
We got to fix this.
That's exactly what
we're going to do.
Oh, this is bad.
Did-did anything else change?
One thing.
Lois bought popsicles for Meg
since that's
all she can eat now.
Mmm, so good. What's yours?
-Apple.
-Aw, there's apple?
I thought that was lime.
But we should...
we should go fix
the Meg-burned-face thing,
though, right?
Yeah, yeah. All right.
Oh, hey, you guys.
I also got ice cream
sandwiches for Meg.
It's a time machine.
We can leave whenever we want.
I mean, we make the schedule.
Yeah. Like, literally.
Jon Hamm.
Arnold Palmer.
The third one's just a mirror.
Oh, wait a minute.
Scratcher!
Peter? It's the middle
of the night.
What the hell are you doing?
-Uh... having an affair?
-What? With who?
You-you don't know her.
Her-her name is...
...Sandy Shoes.
Peter, are you just looking
at stuff in the car
and making up lies?
Lois, that is completely
speedometer.
Look, I don't know
what any of this is,
but just don't turn on
the bathroom light
when you come to bed.
Okay, tha-thank you.
Th-Thanks for no more questions,
love you.
Mr. Griffin,
you're under arrest for--
I know, I know.
How'd you find me?
The store security camera
caught you checking your height
against the doorjamb sticker.
I'm afraid I'm shrinking.
We're gonna measure again
at the jail, though, right?
All right, we're back at the day
of Chris's book report.
To save Meg's face,
we just have to do two things.
First, we lock up the Chris
who successfully gave his report
without incident.
-Flaccid Chris.
-Yes. Ew, ew, gross, but yes.
And then we restore the laughter
that will distract Meg
by releasing the original Chris
from the custodial closet--
Turgid Chris.
You think you're clever,
but you're not clever.
Look, there's Flaccid me.
Happy? Now your crudeness is
a whole thing.
Okay, gonna stop you
right there, bud.
Stewie? Aw, crap, this
can't be good.
Hey, Chris,
we're gonna need you to--
-Stewie, we've got a problem.
-What? What's wrong?
It seems that, given even
a few minutes alone
in a locked closet, Chris, uh...
took matters into his own hands.
-What?
-Yeah, he's in there sleeping
and muttering about
Lola Bunny from Space Jam.
-Who's that?
-A smoking hot rabbit.
Okay, I didn't get it when
you said it, but now I get it.
-So, what do we do now?
-Don't worry. I've got this.
Chris, your book report
is back on.
But... this time you've got
to do it at full mast.
Yeah, um, one small issue
with that:
during the time
you two were yakking
about how the me in the closet
just masturbated...
I, too, masturbated.
-What?!
-Oh, for God's sake.
Damn it! We're running
out of time to save Meg.
Chris, we've got less than
one minute to get you aroused.
Um... okay.
Close your eyes.
You're a 19th-century heiress,
alone in her vast estate
and awaiting a visit
from the handsome vicar,
as her dear aunt has recently
passed from consumption...
Yeah, that-that's nothing.
Well, I'm not proud
of what I'm about
to say here, but...
go to YouTube and type in,
"Brazilian Women's Olympic
Volleyball Team Practice."
They're all speaking Spanish.
Is that part of it for you?
-Portuguese, but yes.
-You guys, you guys, stop.
I'll just type in
"Lauren Boebert
mutual groping vaping
in public Beetlejuice."
Oh, you kind of sexy liar.
I'm ready.
He's a good kid.
I'm proud of him.
What's everyone laughing about?
Which one is Derek's locker?
He can't find
his anti-seizure medicine.
Hey, just so you know,
I can eat 50 eggs.
You already told me
that four times.
Okay, well, 50 sometimes
sounds like 15,
so I just wanted to make sure
you were properly impressed.
Huh. What are you guys
doing here?
Ain't you all
too good for me now?
Peter, we never felt that way.
Yeah, we were
the ones who wanted you
to buy scratchers with us
in the first place.
That's why we've come
to bail you out.
Bail me out? Seriously?
Uh, look, I'm sorry
I overreacted, you guys.
I think I was just frustrated
about never actually
winning anything.
Peter, of course
you're a winner.
You've got a beautiful wife,
a family who loves you,
and-and a bathroom window
that's not as frosted
as you think.
And you're white.
That's a big one.
Oh, yeah.
My insulated experience
of the world
always makes me forget that.
We pooled our last 15 dollars
of scratcher winnings
to pay your fine.
-50 dollars?
-No, 15.
See? This, that-that's,
this is the thing
that I was saying.
Man, you guys are the best.
I hope you can forgive me
for acting so crazy.
Of course we do, Peter.
Wait a second.
You got me out of jail
for only 15 dollars
after I committed a robbery?
Well, I, uh,
pulled a few strings.
Kind of an easy sell to
the Chief because you're white.
See? There's that, there's
that thing that I was saying.
Are we for sure in the clear?
How's Meg?
Mom, have you seen Meg?
Yeah, she went to the store.
Well, I'm sure she's fine.
To pick up some ointment.
For her vagina.
Oh, bit of a journey,
but we got there.
Listen, Stewie,
we never should've used
your time machine
without telling you.
Chris and I owe you an apology.
It's fine, Brian.
At least your heart was
in the right place.
Yeah, well, that's the thing.
I'm... I'm not sure it was.
You see, Chris,
I never should've suggested
a do-over on your book report.
What? Why not?
Well, I realize now
that all the awkward,
embarrassing, difficult
experiences in life are exactly
what shape people
into interesting adults.
You need these cringey moments.
Because I know you have a very
interesting future ahead of you.
-Thanks, Brian.
-You know what?
Maybe let's put a pin in the hug
until that book report pistol's
back in its holster.
Eh, that could just be
time-travel-related.
-From the reentry.
-R-Really?
Yeah, you know how you can get
rando boners on airplanes?
-It's like that.
-Oh, that's right.
The first person
it ever happened to
was Charles Lindbergh.
Here's Lucky Lindbergh landig
in the City of Lights.
And like all great pilots,
he's emerged from the cockpit
with a Betty Boop beach towel
around his waist.
I am perfectly limp,
and what the Nazis do is
an internal matter.
What's going on, guys?
It's me, Corey,
with After the "Guy."
We've only got a minute
to break down
all the best guy moments
from this week.
And, as always, we're brought
to you by too many sponsors.
Peter, what did you think
of the episode?
Well, Corey, I'd say most of it
was freaking sweet,
just like squeezable
Smucker's jelly,
now with a spillproof top.
And even if there was
a plot hole or two,
they're no match for Flex Tape.
Flex Tape: stick it in a drawer,
forget you have it,
then buy it again
three years later.
Okay, question for Stewie.
"Who can understand the baby?"
Okay, as I've explained for
the last six of these, Corey--
He-he had to leave.
He's boxing Jake Paul tonight.
Closing credits
under theme song.
Is there a way to highlight
just the words he has to say?